So we know the polite phrases when we're asking for information when we're making an inquiry or an inquiry.
因此，当我们进行询问或询问时，我们知道询问信息时的礼貌用语。
And we now know how to if we need to call the landlord and make an inquiry or ask the landlord for more
如果我们需要打电话给房东并进行询问或向房东询问更多信息，我们现在知道该怎么做
information about the apartment before we go to look at it.
关于公寓的信息，我们先去看看。
Hopefully you feel very comfortable with that and you can actually do it.
希望您对此感到非常自在，并且您实际上可以做到。
Now what I'd like to do is just quickly talk about some different ways you can say You're welcome.
现在我想做的只是快速谈谈你可以说不客气的一些不同方式。
After you thank somebody who has maybe given you information you need to say thank you.
在你感谢可能给你信息的人之后，你需要说声谢谢。
And then they might say you're welcome.
然后他们可能会说不客气。
You can say thanks.
你可以说谢谢。
You can say I appreciate it but let's look at different ways that people can say You're welcome.
你可以说我很感激，但让我们看看人们可以用不同的方式说“不客气”。
These are the first ones are pretty informal.
这些是第一个非常非正式的。
So these are things you would say to your friends if you say sure sure sure.
因此，如果您说肯定肯定肯定，那么这些就是您会对您的朋友说的话。
Thanks a lot.
非常感谢。
Sure.
当然。
Can I borrow a pen.
我可以借一支笔吗？
Yes or Sure.
是或确定。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Sure you can say it again.
你当然可以再说一遍。
Sure can be used in many ways sometimes yep if it's very quick if you hold the door for somebody you
当然可以用在很多方面
hold the door they go in they say oh thanks you go yep yep.
握住他们进去的门，他们说哦，谢谢你去，是的，是的。
Very quick very informal not formal not formal.
非常快速非常非正式不正式不正式。
OK.
好的。
How about.
怎么样。
Of course this is a little bit more and you can use this in lots of different situations.
当然，这有点多，您可以在许多不同的情况下使用它。
OK.
好的。
So hey do you think you could.
所以，嘿，你认为你可以。
Do you think you could maybe help me with my homework.
你觉得你能不能帮我做作业。
Of course that means yes or Sure.
当然，这意味着是或确定。
That means yes.
这意味着是的。
And then I'll thank you so much.
然后我会非常感谢你。
Then you can again say of course.
那你当然可以再说一遍。
So sometimes these mean both.
所以有时这些意味着两者。
Yes.
是的。
And of course these three all mean.
当然，这三个都意味着。
And they mean you're welcome.
他们的意思是不客气。
Thank you very much.
非常感谢。
Of course.
当然。
Sure.
是的。
No worries no worries.
不用担心不用担心。
Again this is one that is usually informal informal and when you're helping out a good friend they say
同样，这通常是非正式的非正式的，当您帮助好朋友时，他们会说
Oh thanks man.
哦，谢谢伙计。
Aw thanks a lot.
非常感谢。
And no worries no worries.
而且不用担心不用担心。
Thanks for helping me move my sofa today.
谢谢你今天帮我搬沙发。
I know that it was inconvenient.
我知道这很不方便。
No worries.
不用担心。
Don't worry about it.
别担心。
Sometimes people will say don't worry about it.
有时人们会说不要担心。
That's this one down here.
就是下面这个。
OK.
好的。
Sometimes if it's very quick and you're not even paying attention.
有时如果它非常快而你甚至没有注意。
Oh hey thanks by the way thanks for sending out that email for me.
哦，嘿，顺便感谢您为我发送那封电子邮件。
Huh huh.
呵呵。
No problem.
没问题。
That's a very quick one and you would use it only when maybe you're in a rush or you're focused on something
这是一个非常快速的方法，只有在您赶时间或专注于某事时才会使用它
else.
别的。
OK.
好的。
Now the more formal ones a little bit more formal obviously you're welcome.
现在更正式的更正式一点，显然你是受欢迎的。
Happy to help.
乐意效劳。
This is something that somebody may be in customer service might say Oh happy to help.
这可能是客户服务人员可能会说的哦，很乐意提供帮助。
Happy to help or if maybe I help one of my students and my student says thank you for helping me correct
很乐意提供帮助，或者如果我帮助我的一位学生，我的学生说谢谢你帮助我纠正
this.
这个。
I might say Happy to help.
我可能会说乐于助人。
Happy to help.
乐意效劳。
I won't say Happy to help.
我不会说乐于助人。
I'll say happy to happy to happy to help.
我会说乐于助人，乐于助人。
OK this one I think is very formal and I don't use it very often.
好的，我认为这个很正式，我不经常使用它。
My pleasure.
我的荣幸。
In customer service you do hear it.
在客户服务中，您确实听到了。
So if you call somebody.
所以如果你打电话给某人。
My computer's broken.
我的电脑坏了。
And then they help you fix your computer or whatever and then you say Oh thank you so much for helping
然后他们帮你修电脑或其他什么，然后你说哦，非常感谢你的帮助
me.
我。
It might say that's my pleasure.
它可能会说这是我的荣幸。
It's my pleasure.
这是我的荣幸。
I use it once in a while but it's pretty formal so I don't use it that much.
我偶尔会使用它，但它非常正式，所以我不怎么使用它。
OK.
好的。
No sweat.
没有汗水。
This one this one sometimes is used in customer service but it could also go up here in the ones that
这个这个这个有时用于客户服务，但它也可以在那些
are not so formal.
没有那么正式。
These two are similar to no sweat but can be used in many different situations.
这两个类似于没有汗水，但可以在许多不同的情况下使用。
Not at all and no big deal no big deal.
一点也不，没什么大不了的。
Again thank you so much for helping me do my homework yesterday.
再次感谢你昨天帮我做作业。
No big deal no big deal.
没什么大不了的。
Not at all not at all.
一点也不，一点也不。
Don't worry about it.
别担心。
Same thing.
一样。
OK.
好的。
So these are all really really common and they can be used in lots of different situations and sometimes
所以这些都是非常常见的，它们可以在很多不同的情况下使用，有时
forget it forget it forget it.
忘记它忘记它忘记它。
That means you don't even need to talk about it.
这意味着你甚至不需要谈论它。
Forget it.
忘了它。
Right.
正确的。
So those are some of the different ways that we can say you're welcome in different situations.
所以这些是我们可以说在不同情况下欢迎你的一些不同方式。
You've got to listen out for where they're used and how they're used because again sometimes they're
你必须留意它们在哪里使用以及它们是如何使用的，因为有时它们又是
used formally and sometimes not formally.
正式使用，有时不正式使用。
You really have to pay attention to the situation.
你真的要注意情况。
They're used in but hopefully now you know more ways that you can say you're welcome.
它们已被使用，但希望现在您知道更多可以说不受欢迎的方式。
So to practice this what you can do is go on to the Internet maybe go to Craigslist or Zillow or any
所以要练习这个，你可以做的是上网，也许去 Craigslist 或 Zillow 或任何
other site and find an English apartment listing or English apartment post something that you're maybe
其他网站并找到英文公寓列表或英文公寓发布您可能感兴趣的内容
interested in and read it and then do a phone call a role play record yourself between both people the
感兴趣并阅读它然后打个电话角色扮演记录自己在两个人之间
landlord yourself and if you can get a friend involved if you can get a friend to do it with you.
房东自己，如果您可以让朋友参与，是否可以让朋友与您一起做。
That's great.
那太棒了。
You can do it together.
你可以一起做。
Could be really fun do it several different times.
做几次不同的事情可能真的很有趣。
Make sure to record it so that you can listen to it again and pick out where you might actually improve
确保将其录制下来，以便您可以再次聆听并挑选出您可以实际改进的地方
things that you said that might be strange.
你说的话可能很奇怪。
Make sure to try to use some of the words and phrases that we talked about in this lesson.
确保尝试使用我们在本课中谈到的一些单词和短语。
All right good luck.
好吧祝你好运。